I have nothing right now
I know, that's why I chose you
Since Miss Su said the wedding continues
I'll play along
Continue the ceremony
Weren't we at the vows just now
Continue
A wedding is not a game
You should say that to yourself first
I'm not trying to embarrass you
I just want you to see clearly
You're not my only option
Are you willing to stand by my side
And finish this wedding
I am
Does this need confirmation
from both parents
No need
You just made me sign the annulment
statement, which you all agreed to
Since I have called off the engagement
Who I choose now is my own business
Fair enough
If Mr Gu can change his bride
Of course she can change her groom
Are you sure you won't regret this
What I fear isn't regret
Then what is it
It's knowing who is worth choosing